<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/justudios/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/justudios/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-04-23T10:30:02-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/justudios/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Justudios</title><subtitle>Justudios - Web Developer &amp; Furniture Maker</subtitle><author><name>Justin Flowers</name></author><entry><title type="html">Why Javascript?</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/justudios/2019/04/23/javascript.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Why Javascript?" /><published>2019-04-23T05:06:00-05:00</published><updated>2019-04-23T05:06:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/justudios/2019/04/23/javascript</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/justudios/2019/04/23/javascript.html">&lt;p&gt;A lot of people have asked me what language I prefer to code in, and for now my answer is Javascript. Why do I prefer it over other languages?  The main reason is that you can do just about anything with Javascript.  With one simple language you can spin up a server, write APIs, and write a user interface.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Javascript is easy to learn&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Javascript is easy to learn, at least the basics. Yes, there is a barrier to entry when you start talking about Angular, Typescript, React, etc... but if you want to just build stuff with Javascript you can. You only need a text editor to get started.  Once you learn the basics, you can then start learning something more specialized like React or Angular.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Javascript is versatile&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Javascript can be full stack, meaning that it can be the language used to create your APIs as-well-as your front end code. I like the idea of having a single developer being able to easily work with the back end code as-well-as the front end code. This is easier to do when the language used on both the UI (User Interface) and the API (Application Programming Interface) is the same.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;You can even do styling with Javascript. This isn't always the best use of Javascript, but styling in Javascript can be very powerful when building components in React.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Go Mobile! Mobile apps can be built with Javascript now.  Sure, you might get to a point where you'll need a little more than just Javascript but you can get pretty far with React Native or Phone Gap.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Build desktop apps. With electron, you can build desktop apps with Javascript. VSCode, Microsofts free editor, uses the Electron framework.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt;Javascript has a ton of tutorials, packages, and documentation&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This is both a blessing and a curse. The great news is that there is a ton of information about Javascript on the internet. It's easy to find tutorials and documentation on just about anything you can think of. The issue with that? Some times it can be hard to find things that are up to date or packages that are still being maintained. There's a lot of garbage mixed in with the good content, but overall I'd still say this is a plus.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Justin Flowers</name></author><summary type="html">A lot of people have asked me what language I prefer to code in, and for now my answer is Javascript. Why do I prefer it over other languages? The main reason is that you can do just about anything with Javascript. With one simple language you can spin up a server, write APIs, and write a user interface. Javascript is easy to learn Javascript is easy to learn, at least the basics. Yes, there is a barrier to entry when you start talking about Angular, Typescript, React, etc... but if you want to just build stuff with Javascript you can. You only need a text editor to get started. Once you learn the basics, you can then start learning something more specialized like React or Angular. Javascript is versatile Javascript can be full stack, meaning that it can be the language used to create your APIs as-well-as your front end code. I like the idea of having a single developer being able to easily work with the back end code as-well-as the front end code. This is easier to do when the language used on both the UI (User Interface) and the API (Application Programming Interface) is the same. You can even do styling with Javascript. This isn't always the best use of Javascript, but styling in Javascript can be very powerful when building components in React. Go Mobile! Mobile apps can be built with Javascript now. Sure, you might get to a point where you'll need a little more than just Javascript but you can get pretty far with React Native or Phone Gap. Build desktop apps. With electron, you can build desktop apps with Javascript. VSCode, Microsofts free editor, uses the Electron framework. Javascript has a ton of tutorials, packages, and documentation This is both a blessing and a curse. The great news is that there is a ton of information about Javascript on the internet. It's easy to find tutorials and documentation on just about anything you can think of. The issue with that? Some times it can be hard to find things that are up to date or packages that are still being maintained. There's a lot of garbage mixed in with the good content, but overall I'd still say this is a plus.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">My first post</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/justudios/2019/04/22/first-post.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="My first post" /><published>2019-04-22T08:46:00-05:00</published><updated>2019-04-22T08:46:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/justudios/2019/04/22/first-post</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/justudios/2019/04/22/first-post.html">&lt;p&gt;Thanks for stopping by. I mostly use this domain to communicate with my clients. If you would like to get in touch with me please fill out the form on the contact page.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I love working with people on web projects and helping them grow their business. One of the simplest things to do is to have a website where people can learn about your business. You may think that you took care of that back in 1999, but what good is a website if people can't find it, the information isn't up to date, or a user can't browse your site on their mobile phone. My goal is to make the web a better place, 1 site at a time. If you need someone to update your website, make your website look great on all devices, or even help getting your company found on Google than you have come to the right place.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt; Here's a list of some of the services I am currently offering customers:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Updating Website Content&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Making Mobile Friendly, Tablet and Phone, Versions Of Websites&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Developing &amp; Implementing SEO (Search Engine Optimization) Strategies&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Creating Analytic Reporting and Visitor Insight&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Fixing Bugs In Websites Or Code Written By Other 3rd Party Companies&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Building SPA (Single Page Applications) With React&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Creating An E-Commerce Store&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt; I can do a lot more than that, but that's currently the projects that I am working on with some of my clients. If you want to see if I can work with you on your next project send me an email on my contact form or visit me on linkedin below.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Justin Flowers</name></author><summary type="html">Thanks for stopping by. I mostly use this domain to communicate with my clients. If you would like to get in touch with me please fill out the form on the contact page. I love working with people on web projects and helping them grow their business. One of the simplest things to do is to have a website where people can learn about your business. You may think that you took care of that back in 1999, but what good is a website if people can't find it, the information isn't up to date, or a user can't browse your site on their mobile phone. My goal is to make the web a better place, 1 site at a time. If you need someone to update your website, make your website look great on all devices, or even help getting your company found on Google than you have come to the right place. Here's a list of some of the services I am currently offering customers: Updating Website Content Making Mobile Friendly, Tablet and Phone, Versions Of Websites Developing &amp; Implementing SEO (Search Engine Optimization) Strategies Creating Analytic Reporting and Visitor Insight Fixing Bugs In Websites Or Code Written By Other 3rd Party Companies Building SPA (Single Page Applications) With React Creating An E-Commerce Store I can do a lot more than that, but that's currently the projects that I am working on with some of my clients. If you want to see if I can work with you on your next project send me an email on my contact form or visit me on linkedin below.</summary></entry></feed>