<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.8.5">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/justudios/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/justudios/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2019-04-22T13:57:49-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/justudios/feed.xml</id><title type="html">Justudios</title><subtitle>Justudios - Web Developer &amp; Furniture Maker</subtitle><author><name>Justin Flowers</name></author><entry><title type="html">My first post</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/justudios/2019/04/22/first-post.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="My first post" /><published>2019-04-22T08:46:00-05:00</published><updated>2019-04-22T08:46:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/justudios/2019/04/22/first-post</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/justudios/2019/04/22/first-post.html">&lt;p&gt;Thanks for stopping by. I mostly use this domain to communicate with my clients. If you would like to get in touch with me please fill out the form on the contact page.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I love working with people on web projects and helping them grow their business. One of the simplest things to do is to have a website where people can learn about your business. You may think that you took care of that back in 1999, but what good is a website if people can't find it, the information isn't up to date, or a user can't browse your site on their mobile phone. My goal is to make the web a better place, 1 site at a time. If you need someone to update your website, make your website look great on all devices, or even help getting your company found on Google than you have come to the right place.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3&gt; Here's a list of some of the services I am currently offering customers:&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Updating Website Content&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Making Mobile Friendly, Tablet and Phone, Versions Of Websites&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Developing &amp; Implementing SEO (Search Engine Optimization) Strategies&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Creating Analytic Reporting and Visitor Insight&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Fixing Bugs In Websites Or Code Written By Other 3rd Party Companies&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Building SPA (Single Page Applications) With React&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Creating An E-Commerce Store&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt; I can do a lot more than that, but that's currently the projects that I am working on with some of my clients. If you want to see if I can work with you on your next project send me an email on my contact form or visit me on linkedin below.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name>Justin Flowers</name></author><summary type="html">Thanks for stopping by. I mostly use this domain to communicate with my clients. If you would like to get in touch with me please fill out the form on the contact page. I love working with people on web projects and helping them grow their business. One of the simplest things to do is to have a website where people can learn about your business. You may think that you took care of that back in 1999, but what good is a website if people can't find it, the information isn't up to date, or a user can't browse your site on their mobile phone. My goal is to make the web a better place, 1 site at a time. If you need someone to update your website, make your website look great on all devices, or even help getting your company found on Google than you have come to the right place. Here's a list of some of the services I am currently offering customers: Updating Website Content Making Mobile Friendly, Tablet and Phone, Versions Of Websites Developing &amp; Implementing SEO (Search Engine Optimization) Strategies Creating Analytic Reporting and Visitor Insight Fixing Bugs In Websites Or Code Written By Other 3rd Party Companies Building SPA (Single Page Applications) With React Creating An E-Commerce Store I can do a lot more than that, but that's currently the projects that I am working on with some of my clients. If you want to see if I can work with you on your next project send me an email on my contact form or visit me on linkedin below.</summary></entry></feed>